export const FullStackQuizData = [
    {
        question: "Full stack developers work on?",
        options: ["Frontend", "Backend", "Both", "None"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which language is not used in full stack?",
        options: ["HTML", "CSS", "SQL", "Swift"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does MVC stand for in web development?",
        options: ["Model-View-Controller", "Main-Visual-Code", "Module-View-Component", "Model-View-Collection"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a JavaScript framework commonly used in full stack development?",
        options: ["Django", "Laravel", "React", "Flask"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the primary purpose of Node.js in full stack development?",
        options: ["Styling web pages", "Handling server-side operations", "Designing databases", "Creating animations"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which database is a NoSQL database commonly used in full stack development?",
        options: ["MySQL", "PostgreSQL", "MongoDB", "SQLite"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the role of RESTful APIs in web development?",
        options: ["Designing user interfaces", "Managing server hardware", "Facilitating communication between client and server", "Creating database schemas"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a CSS framework that helps in designing responsive web pages?",
        options: ["Bootstrap", "Angular", "Vue.js", "Express"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In the MERN stack, what does 'M' stand for?",
        options: ["MySQL", "MongoDB", "MariaDB", "Memcached"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which HTTP method is typically used to retrieve data from a server?",
        options: ["POST", "PUT", "DELETE", "GET"],
        answer: 4
    }
];
